Glucksman Ireland House Records AIA.038
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Glucksman Ireland House Activities and Administrative Files, 1907-2002 (inclusive); 1991-2002 (bulk); 3.77 Linear Feet in 5 legal sized manuscript boxes, 1 letter sized manuscript box, 1 half letter sized manuscript box, 1 shared media box, 1 shared CD box, and 1 shared flat box; 1.70 G
  - Film Festival - Correspondence & Faxes, 1997; cuid35254 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Film Festival - Expenses, 1997; cuid35255 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Film Festival - Film Information, 1997; cuid35256 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Film Festival - Fundraising, 1997; cuid35257 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Film Festival - Mailing Lists (and mailing), 1997; cuid35258 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Film Festival - Press Clips & Press Packs, 1997; cuid35259 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - "Framing Her Image: Women in Irish Film" program, undated; cuid35260 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - From Shore to Shore - Original Interview Footage (Andy McGann, Mary Hannon, Mary O'Beirne, Jim O'Beirne), undated; cuid35261 (Box 15, Vhs 038.0019)
  - From Shore to Shore - Original Interview Footage (Maureen Glynn & Maureen Doherty), undated; cuid35262 (Box 15, Vhs 038.0020)
  - From Shore to Shore - Original Interview Footage (Snug Harbor, Dan Collins, McGoverns), undated; cuid35263 (Box 14, Vhs 038.0001)
  - Fundraising General, 1994; cuid35264 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Glucksman Fleash, 1999; cuid35265 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Glucksman Ireland House 1995 Spring Calendar, cuid35266 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Glucksman Ireland House Fall Newsletter, 1996; cuid35267 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Glucksman Ireland House Fall Program, 1995; cuid35268 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Glucksman Ireland House - Fifth Anniversary Celebration, 1998; cuid35269 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Glucksman Ireland House labels, undated; cuid35270 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Glucksman Ireland House membership, undated; cuid35271 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Glucksman Ireland House, New York University - Irish Studies Fund, 1995; cuid35272 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Glucksman Ireland House Public Events Calendar Autumn 1996, cuid35273 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Glucksman Ireland House Spring Calendar, 1996; cuid35274 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - "The Gothic, the National, the Subversive" Symposium on the Irish Gothic, undated; cuid35275 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Grian Conference Register, 2000; cuid35276 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Grimes #1, undated; cuid35277 (Box 14, Vhs 038.0011)
  - Grimes #2, undated; cuid35278 (Box 14, Vhs 038.0012)
  - H Seq 5, 2000; cuid35279 (Box 15, Vhs 038.0017)
  - Hartford Conference, 1998; cuid35280 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Heaney, undated; cuid35281 (Box 15, Betacam sp 038.0023)
  - Hector McDonnell Art Exhibit Postcards, 1997; cuid35282 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - IH 008, undated; cuid35283 (Box 16, Minidv 038.0048)
  - IH Program, Spring 1994, cuid35284 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - IH Staff Meetings, 1998-1999; cuid35285 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Installation of Officers of the County Longford Men's S & B Association and Ladies Auxiliary, 1942; cuid35346 (Box Shared Tamiment 080, Folder 9)
  - International Programs Dublin, 1998-1999; cuid35286 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Ireland House, undated; cuid35287 (Box 14, Vhs 038.0013)
  - Ireland House: Archives of Irish America Tapes Information & Transcripts, 2000-2001; cuid35288 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Ireland House at NYU Membership Application, undated; cuid35289 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Ireland House Press, 1993-1994; cuid35290 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Ireland House Roll #8, 2002; cuid35291 (Box 15, Vhs 038.0015)
  - Ireland House Roll #9, 2002; cuid35292 (Box 15, Vhs 038.0016)
  - Ireland House - Seq. 5/Seq 6, 2000; cuid35293 (Box 16, Minidv 038.0047)
  - Irish Advisory Committee, 1994; cuid35294 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Irish Film Festival - Filmmaker Bios & Contact Sheet, 1997; cuid35295 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Irish Football Team Photos, 1932-1935; cuid35345 (Box Shared Tamiment 080, Folder 8)
  - Irish Hunger Commem. AOH Coalition, 1994; cuid35296 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Irish Institute, 1998; cuid35297 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Irish Language, 1995; cuid35298 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Irish Migration, undated; cuid35299 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Irish Studies Program, 1994-1997; cuid35300 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Irish Studies Program Fall Schedule, 1997-1998; cuid35301 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - "Jameson Global Bloomsday" Program, 1998; cuid35302 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Joe Lee (cont'd) NYU Ireland House CR #4, 2000; cuid35303 (Box 16, Minidv 038.0041)
  - John Feighery, 1943-1962; cuid35304 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - John W. Draper Interdisciplinary Master's Program in Humanities and Social Thought, undated; cuid35305 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - "The Kindgdom of Kerry" - Michael Flaherty Exhibition, 1995; cuid35306 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - L.B.G. Board, undated; cuid35307 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - List of Irish Writers and Books for Bobst, 1993; cuid35308 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Loretta, undated; cuid35309 (Box 15, Betacam sp 038.0022)
  - Loretta Brennan Glucksman, Cormac O'Malley 2, Bob Scally NYU Ireland House CR #2, 2000; cuid35310 (Box 16, Minidv 038.0039)
  - Medieval Search, 1992-1994; cuid35311 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Memorandum, 1995-1997; cuid35312 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - NEH, 1994; cuid35313 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - New Asst. Prof. AD, 1998; cuid35314 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - "New York Stories" - The Archives of Irish America, 2000; cuid35315 (Box 16, Minidv 038.0042)
  - New York Times, 1991, 1994; cuid35316 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - New York University Glucksman Ireland House Promo Video - Seq 5 (Work in Progress), 2000; cuid35317 (Box 15, Vhs 038.0018)
  - New York University Irish Studies, 1997; cuid35318 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Next Door Neighbors: The Irish & others in New York City, 1996; cuid35319 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - NYCH - Bruce Arnold, 1994-1997; cuid35320 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - NYU in Dublin, undated; cuid35321 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - NYU Graduate School of Arts & Sciences Fall Course List, 1998; cuid35322 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - NYU Ireland House Tape #5 Pete Hamill Interview, 2000; cuid35323 (Box 14, Vhs 038.0007, Box 16, Dvcam 038.0024, Minidv 038.0044)
  - NYU Ireland House Tape #6 Pete Hamill Interview Pt. 2, 2000; cuid35324 (Box 14, Vhs 038.0008, Box 16, Dvcam 038.0025, Minidv 038.0045)
  - NYU Ireland House Tape #7 (IH/Bobst Ext.), 2000; cuid35325 (Box 14, Vhs 038.0009, Box 16, Dvcam 038.0026, Minidv 038.0046)
  - NYU Ireland House Tape #8, 2000; cuid35326 (Box 16, Dvcam 038.0027)
  - NYU Ireland House Tape #9, 2000; cuid35327 (Box 16, Dvcam 038.0028)
  - Oliva, Neeson, Richardson, Donaghue, undated; cuid35328 (Box 15, Betacam sp 038.0021)
  - "On Being a Living Fossil: Writing in Irish", undated; cuid35329 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Padraig O'Cearuill, 1994; cuid35330 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Peter Quinn, Joe Lee NYU Ireland House CR #3, 2000; cuid35331 (Box 16, Minidv 038.0040)
  - Post Colonial Conditions Ireland in a Comparative Context - Opening Lectures, undated; cuid35332 (Box 14, Vhs 038.0010)
  - Post-Colonial Conditions: Ireland in a Comparative Context Symposium Programs, 1997; cuid35333 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - RADHARC: Chronicles of Glucksman Ireland House, 2001; cuid35334 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Robert (Roy) Fitzroy CV, 1997; cuid35335 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - RW D'Arcy, 1947; cuid35336 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - "Scannan '96", 1996; cuid35337 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Seamus Deane Notre Dame, 1997; cuid35338 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Seamus Heaney Dinner, 1996; cuid35339 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Topics in Early Modern Europe: Ireland and Scotland in Europe in the 16th and 17th Centuries, 1997; cuid35340 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Visions and Revisions: Recent Trends in Irish History and Literature, 1995; cuid35341 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - "When Time Began to Rant and Rage" Exhibit, undated; cuid35342 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Wild Geese, 1992-1995; cuid35343 (Box 12, Folder 22)